export const dataDisk = [
    { 'path': 'Z', 'ip': '192.168.150.214', 'label': 'broadcast'},
    { 'path': 'Y', 'ip': '192.168.150.213', 'label': 'visualinspector'},
    { 'path': 'X', 'ip': '172.16.45.225', 'label': 'ftp'},
    { 'path': 'W', 'ip': '172.16.45.225', 'label': 'watchdalet'},
    { 'path': 'V', 'ip': '172.16.40.237', 'label': 'export'},
    { 'path': 'U', 'ip': '172.16.45.22', 'label': 'brio01'},
    { 'path': 'T', 'ip': '172.16.45.23', 'label': 'brio02'},
    { 'path': 'S', 'ip': '172.16.45.24', 'label': 'brio03'},
    { 'path': 'R', 'ip': '172.16.40.158', 'label': 'tobeqc'},
]

export const dataTicket = [
    { 'id': '1', 'name': 'Angga Emirisia', 'date': '2021-12-14T01:12:21+07:00', 'department': 'redaksi', 'subject': 'pc newsroom05', 'problem': 'pc newsroom05 tidak bisa connect server 150.214', 'solution': '', 'onduty': ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status': 'closed', 'priority': 'medium', 'history' : [{'id': '1', 'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty': ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': 'test'}, {'id': '2', 'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty': ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status' : 'closed', 'note': 'restart pc mapping ulang'}]  },
    { 'id': '2', 'name': 'Angga Emirisia', 'date': '2021-12-14T11:30:21+07:00', 'department': 'redaksi', 'subject': 'Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text', 'problem': 'user redaksi minta dibuatin shortcut sent to dalet', 'solution': 'create shortcut sent to dalet dari pc vip03', 'onduty': ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status': 'in progress', 'priority': 'low', 'history' : [{'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty': ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': ''}]  },
    { 'id': '3', 'name': 'Angga Emirisia', 'date': '2021-12-14T11:30:21+07:00', 'department': 'redaksi', 'subject': 'shortcut sent to dalet di redaksi06', 'problem': 'user redaksi minta dibuatin shortcut sent to dalet', 'solution': 'create shortcut sent to dalet dari pc vip03', 'onduty': ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status': 'pending', 'priority': 'low', 'history' : [{'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty': ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': ''}]  },
    { 'id': '4', 'name': 'Deni Nurdiana', 'date': '2021-12-14T12:12:21+07:00', 'department': 'mcr', 'subject': 'ntp fw-a itx not sync', 'problem': 'service timesync di fw-a itx tidak sync dengan ntp server 49.123', 'solution': '', 'onduty': ['Deni Nurdiana'], 'note': 'eskalasi ke elnet', 'status': 'escalated', 'priority': 'critical', 'history' : [{'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty': ['Deni Nurdiana'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': ''}]  },
    { 'id': '5', 'name': 'Angga Emirisia', 'date': '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'department': 'editing', 'subject': 'editing gs03', 'problem': 'pc editing gs03 ketika dipakai edit tibe-tibe bluescreen', 'solution': '', 'onduty': ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status': 'pending', 'priority': 'medium', 'history' : [{'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty' : ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': ''}]  },
    { 'id': '6', 'name': 'Angga Emirisia', 'date': '2021-12-14T11:30:21+07:00', 'department': 'redaksi', 'subject': 'shortcut sent to dalet di redaksi06', 'problem': 'user redaksi minta dibuatin shortcut sent to dalet', 'solution': 'create shortcut sent to dalet dari pc vip03', 'onduty': ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status': 'on hold', 'priority': 'low', 'history' : [{'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty' : ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': ''}]  },
    { 'id': '7', 'name': 'Deni Nurdiana', 'date': '2021-12-14T12:12:21+07:00', 'department': 'mcr', 'subject': 'ntp fw-a itx not sync', 'problem': 'service timesync di fw-a itx tidak sync dengan ntp server 49.123', 'solution': '', 'onduty': ['Deni Nurdiana'], 'note': 'eskalasi ke elnet', 'status': 'escalated', 'priority': 'critical', 'history' : [{'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty' : ['Deni Nurdiana'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': ''}]  },
    { 'id': '8', 'name': 'Angga Emirisia', 'date': '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'department': 'editing', 'subject': 'editing gs03', 'problem': 'pc editing gs03 ketika dipakai edit tibe-tibe bluescreen', 'solution': '', 'onduty': ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status': 'in progress', 'priority': 'medium', 'history' : [{'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty' : ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': ''}]  },
    { 'id': '9', 'name': 'Angga Emirisia', 'date': '2021-12-14T11:30:21+07:00', 'department': 'redaksi', 'subject': 'shortcut sent to dalet di redaksi06', 'problem': 'user redaksi minta dibuatin shortcut sent to dalet', 'solution': 'create shortcut sent to dalet dari pc vip03', 'onduty': ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status': 'solved', 'priority': 'low', 'history' : [{'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty' : ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': ''}]  },
    { 'id': '10', 'name': 'Deni Nurdiana', 'date': '2021-12-14T12:12:21+07:00', 'department': 'mcr', 'subject': 'ntp fw-a itx not sync', 'problem': 'service timesync di fw-a itx tidak sync dengan ntp server 49.123', 'solution': '', 'onduty': ['Deni Nurdiana'], 'note': 'eskalasi ke elnet', 'status': 'closed', 'priority': 'critical', 'history' : [{'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty' : ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': ''}]  },
    { 'id': '11', 'name': 'Deni Nurdiana', 'date': '2021-12-14T12:12:21+07:00', 'department': 'mcr', 'subject': 'ntp fw-a itx not sync', 'problem': 'service timesync di fw-a itx tidak sync dengan ntp server 49.123', 'solution': '', 'onduty': ['Deni Nurdiana'], 'note': 'eskalasi ke elnet', 'status': 'closed', 'priority': 'critical', 'history' : [{'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty' : ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': ''}]  },
    { 'id': '12', 'name': 'Deni Nurdiana', 'date': '2021-12-14T12:12:21+07:00', 'department': 'mcr', 'subject': 'ntp fw-a itx not sync', 'problem': 'service timesync di fw-a itx tidak sync dengan ntp server 49.123', 'solution': '', 'onduty': ['Deni Nurdiana'], 'note': 'eskalasi ke elnet', 'status': 'closed', 'priority': 'critical', 'history' : [{'date' : '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00', 'onduty' : ['Angga Emirisia', 'Neldo Joseph'], 'status' : 'open', 'note': ''}]  },
]

export const dataReportProgram = [
    { 'id': '1', 'program': 'metro pagi primetime', 'onduty': ['Angga Eirisia', 'Neldo'], 'onair': 'aman', 'dalet': 'aman', 'description': '', 'pd': 'haru', 'date': '2021-12-14T10:12:21+07:00' }
]

export const dataReportLive = [
    { 'id': '1', 'program': 'top news', 'onduty': ['Angga Eirisia', 'Neldo'], 'pukul': '2022-04-02T21:05:21+07:00', 'unit': 'TVU 10', 'server': '6', 'modemup': '6', 'lokasi': 'jogja', 'description': '', 'date': '2022-04-02T21:15:21+07:00' }
]

export const dataChecklist = [
    { 'id': '1', 'day': '2022-04-02T11:00:00+07:00', 'time': '2022-04-02T11:00:00+07:00', 'onduty': ['Angga Eirisia', 'Neldo'], 'encoder': ['graphic', 'vip03', 'it02-pcr1'], 'batchfiles': ['amberfine', 'dalet-itx', 'xtend', 'aptn'], 'wires': ['aptn'], 'storage': [{'name': 'script_backup', 'ip': '192.168.150.204'}], 'itx': '', 'dalet': '', 'date': '2022-04-02T11:15:21+07:00' }
]